Guide to the Sisterhood is Global Institute Records, 1963-2010 and undated, bulk 1980-2002 RL.01185
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files Series, 1975-2004 and undated, 49 boxes
  - Funding Files Subseries, 1984-2002 and undated
    - Administrative general (Box FF2)
      - Private sector funding, info, 2000 (Box FF2)
      - Sample funding proposals, 1997 (Box FF2)
      - SIGI donations in kind, 1995 (Box FF2)
      - SIGI website, 2000 (Box FF2)
    - Aga Khan Network, info, 1999-2001 (Box FF3)
    - AIDOS, correspondence, 1998 (Box FF3)
    - Alcoa Foundation, info, 2000 (Box FF3)
    - America's Development Foundation, inquiry, 1998 June 30 (Box FF3)
    - Asia Foundation, info, 2001 (Box FF3)
    - AVON Foundation, info, 2000 (Box FF3)
    - Bertelsmann Foundation, info, inquiry, 1998 (Box FF3)
    - Bill Gates Foundation, info, inquiry, 2000 (Box FF3)
    - Boehm Foundation, correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box FF3)
    - Bradley Foundation, HRE manual, grant, 1996-1998 (Box FF3)
    - Bydale Foundation, inquiry, 1998 Sept. 15 (Box FF3)
    - Calmeadow, annual report, 1998-1999 (Box FF3)
    - Canadian funding
      - Letter to the The Gazette, 2000 Dec. 4 (Box FF3)
      - Le Château, project proposals, 2000-2001 (Box FF3)
      - National Public Relations Inc, correspondence, 2000 Nov. 28 (Box FF3)
    - Canadian Women's Foundation, info, 2000-2001 (Box FF3)
    - Capital Area United Way, correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box FF3)
    - Careth Foundation, info, 1998, 2000, 2 folders (Box FF3)
    - Carnegie Foundation, info, 1998, 2000, 2 folders (Box FF3)
    - Carrie Chapman Catt Center, info, letter, 1995 (Box FF3)
    - Center for the Study of the Gift Economy
      - Fisheries, general support, 2000 (Box FF3)
      - Original proposal, 1997-2000 (Box FF3)
    - Combined Federal Campaign for Greater Los Angelis (CFC)
      - Applications
        - For 1997 campaign, correspondence, 1996-1998, 2 folders (Box FF3)
        - For 1998 campaign (Box FF3)
        - Funding for 1998 (Box FF3)
        - For 1999 campaign (Box FF3)
    - Combined Federal Campaign for Greater Los Angelis (CFC) (Box FF4)
      - Applications
        - Funding for 1999, 1999-2001 (Box FF4)
        - Letters of thanks for 1999 campaign (Box FF4)
      - Correspondence, 2000 (Box FF4)
      - Renewal for 2001 campaign, 2000 (Box FF4)
      - SIGI change of address, 2000 (Box FF4)
    - Charitable way
      - Profile changes (Box FF4)
      - Check summary report, 2001 (Box FF4)
    - Charles Steward Mott Foundation, info, 1998, 2001, 2 folders (Box FF4)
    - Christian Aid, info, 2001 (Box FF4)
    - Christopher Reynolds, info, 1998 (Box FF4)
    - Church Women United, info, 1998, 2001, 2 folders (Box FF4)
    - Canadian International Development Agency (CIDA)
      - Correspondence, 1998-2000, 2 folders (Box FF4)
      - Initial Approach project proposals, 2000 (Box FF4)
      - Proposal guidelines, 1999-2000 (Box FF4)
      - Afghanistan, 2000 (Box FF4)
      - Paterson, Maggie, 2001 (Box FF4)
    - Cissy Patterson Trust Fund
      - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box FF4)
      - Grant proposal, reports, 1999-2000 (Box FF4)
      - Correspondence, 2000 (Box FF4)
    - Citicorp account, 2002 (Box FF4)
    - Clark Foundation, 1993
      - Grant (Box FF4)
      - Project (Box FF4)
    - Columbia Foundation, 1998 (Box FF4)
    - Commonwealth Foundation, 1998 (Box FF4)
    - Compton Foundation, info, 2001 (Box FF4)
    - C.S. Fund, funding request, 1997-1998 (Box FF4)
    - CUSO, inquiry, 1998 (Box FF4)
    - David and Lucie Packard Foundation, info, 1998, 2000 (Box FF4)
    - Dougherty Foundation
      - Grants, 1995-1999 (Box FF4)
      - Correspondence, report, 1996-1998 (Box FF5)
      - Vaughan, Genevieve, correspondence, 2000 July (Box FF5)
    - Doris Duke Foundation, info, 2001 (Box FF5)
    - eGrants, info, 2001 (Box FF5)
    - European Human Rights Foundation, info, 1998 (Box FF5)
    - Flatiron Foundation, info, 2001 (Box FF5)
    - Ford Foundation
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1992-1995, 1997, 1999, 4 folders (Box FF5)
        - Back, Aaron, 2000 (Box FF5)
        - Sullivan, Barbara, 2000-2001 (Box FF5)
      - Information, 1994-2000, 2 folders (Box FF5)
      - Beijing and Beyond: Implementing the Platform for Action in Muslim Societies conference, 1996-1997, 3 folders (Box FF5)
      - Funding requests, 1998 (Box FF5)
      - Proposal guidelines, 2000 (Box FF5)
    - Foundation for a Compassionate Society
      - Materials, 1993-1994 (Box FF5)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1994 Sept. 23, 1999 Nov. 1 (Box FF5)
        - Vaughan, Genevieve, 1993-1997 (Box FF5)
    - Foundation de France, info, 1998 (Box FF5)
    - France Libertés, Fondation Danielle Mitterrand, info, inquiry, 1998 (Box FF5)
    - Funding exchange
      - Guidelines and materials, 1996-1998 (Box FF5)
      - Ignacia Martín-Baró Fund, forms, 2000 (Box FF5)
    - Gaea Foundation (Box FF6)
      - Grants, 1996-1999, annual report, 1999 (Box FF6)
      - Final report, 2000 (Box FF6)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box FF6)
      - Information, 2000 (Box FF6)
    - General Service Foundation, info, 1997-1998 (Box FF6)
    - German Marshall Fund of the US, info, 1998 (Box FF6)
    - Global Fund for Women
      - Correspondence, 1996-2001, 2 folders (Box FF6)
      - Materials, 1996-1999 (Box FF6)
      - Rights of Passage conference, 1997 (Box FF6)
      - Eliminating Violence against Women (Jordan) conference, 1998 (Box FF6)
      - Eliminating Violence against Women project, phases I, II, 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box FF6)
      - Expert Group meeting, 1998-1999 (Box FF6)
      - Project proposal with Cemina, 1999 (Box FF6)
      - Funding request for SIGI/Jordan, 1998-1999 (Box FF6)
      - Proposal guidelines and funding requests, 2000-2001 (Box FF6)
    - Grassroots International, correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box FF6)
    - Greenville Foundation, info, 1998-2000 (Box FF6)
    - Hadassah Foundation, correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box FF6)
    - Hanns Seidel Stiftung Institute for Foreign Relations, inquiry, 1998 (Box FF6)
    - Harry Frank Guggenheim Foundation, info, 1998 (Box FF6)
    - Helen Bader Foundation, info, 2000 (Box FF6)
    - International Center for Human Rights and Democratic Development (ICHRDD)
      - Correspondence, SIGI activities, 1991-1996, 2 folders (Box FF6)
      - Eliminating Violence against Women (VAW) project (Box FF7)
        - Project proposals, research reports, 1997 (Box FF7)
        - Interim reports, 1997-2000, 2 folders (Box FF7)
        - Helal, Solon Isabelle, 2000 Feb. 3 (Box FF7)
        - Final report, 2001 (Box FF7)
      - Correspondence, 2001 (Box FF7)
      - Droits des Femmes, Middle East meeting, 2001 (Box FF7)
    - International Development Research Center, info, 2001 (Box FF7)
    - Independent Charities of America, correspondence, 1998 (Box FF7)
    - Institute for the Study of Natural and Cultural Resources
      - Grant, 1998 (Box FF7)
      - Report of activities, 1998-1999, grant correspondence, 1998 (Box FF7)
      - Correspondence, 2000 (Box FF7)
    - United Nations International Research and Training Institute for the Advancement of Women (INSTRAW)
      - Project proposal, 2000-2001 (Box FF7)
      - Agreement, 2001 (Box FF7)
      - GAINS, correspondence, 2000-2001, 2 folders (Box FF7)
      - Afghan women, 2001 (Box FF7)
      - Contract, 2001 July (Box FF7)
      - Correspondence, 2001 (Box FF7)
      - Project proposals, 2001 (Box FF7)
    - Inter-American Foundation, info, 1998 (Box FF7)
    - International Women Health Coalition, info, 1998 (Box FF7)
    - Jacobs Family Foundation, materials, 1998 (Box FF7)
    - Jacob Blaustein Institute (Box FF8)
      - Correspondence with Gaer Felice, 1997-1998 (Box FF8)
      - Information, 1997-2000 (Box FF8)
    - J.C. Downing Foundation, info, request, 2000 (Box FF8)
    - J. Roderick MacArthur Foundation, correspondence, 1989-1994 (Box FF8)
    - Japan Women in Development Fund, info, 2001 (Box FF8)
    - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation
      - Grants, 1998-2000 (Box FF8)
      - Materials, proposals, 1998-2000 (Box FF8)
      - KPP reports
        - 1999 (Box FF8)
        - Final, 2000 Oct. 30 (Box FF8)
      - Materials, HRE financial report, 1999-2000 (Box FF8)
      - Donations, 2000 (Box FF8)
      - Project proposals, 2000 (Box FF8)
      - Info, correspondence, 2001 (Box FF8)
      - Inquiries, 2001 (Box FF8)
    - Joyce-Mertz-Gilmore Foundation
      - Correspondence, proposals, 1995-2001, 2 folders (Box FF8)
      - KPP proposal, 2000 (Box FF8)
      - Project proposal, 2000 (Box FF8)
      - Correspondence with J. DiPerna, 2000-2001 (Box FF8)
    - KeySpan Foundation, correspondence, info, 2000-2001 (Box FF8)
    - King Baudouin Foundation, correspondence, 1996 (Box FF8)
    - Konrad Adenauer Foundation, materials, correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box FF9)
    - Light, Deborah Ann, correspondence, 1989-1998, 2000-2001, 3 folders (Box FF9)
    - Mama Cash
      - Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box FF9)
      - Information, 2000 (Box FF9)
      - Inquiry, 2000 (Box FF9)
    - Markle Foundation, info, 2000 (Box FF9)
    - MATCH International Center, info, 1998 (Box FF9)
    - Max and Anna Levinson Foundation, correspondence, 1997 (Box FF9)
    - McKnight Foundation, info, 1998 (Box FF9)
    - Moriah Fund, correspondence, 2000 (Box FF9)
    - Ms. Foundation for Women
      - Information, 1998-1999 (Box FF9)
      - Information, correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box FF9)
      - Inquiry, 2001 (Box FF9)
    - Nathan Cummings Foundation
      - Funding request, 1997-1998 (Box FF9)
      - Inquiry, 2000 (Box FF9)
    - National Democratic Institute for International Affairs, inquiry, 1998 (Box FF9)
    - National Semiconductor Corporation, SIGI's tax-exempt status, 2000 (Box FF9)
    - National Endowment for Democracy (NED)
      - Guidelines for NED grantees
        - General, 1994 (Box FF9)
        - NED status, Appendix A-F, undated (Box FF9)
        - Sample proposals, 1995-1996 (Box FF9)
        - Women's Human Rights Education in the Muslim World project proposal, 1995 July (Box FF9)
      - Grant agreement, 1995-1996
        - Agreement and amendments, 1995 (Box FF9)
        - Budget, provisions (Box FF9)
        - Extension approval, 1996 (Box FF9)
        - Financial information (Box FF9)
        - Paris Conference proposal, undated (Box FF9)
        - People's Decade of Human Rights Education, correspondence, 1995 Nov. 21 (Box FF9)
        - Period reports, 1995-1996 (Box FF9)
      - Grant, 1996-1997
        - Authorization forms (Box FF9)
        - Drawdown, 1997 (Box FF9)
        - Financial information (Box FF9)
    - NED (Box FF10)
      - Grant, 1996-1997
        - Financial and periodic reports (Box FF10)
        - Grant correspondence (Box FF10)
        - Notification of grant approval, manual, part I, phase II (Box FF10)
        - Periodic reports (Box FF10)
        - Proposals, part II, phase I (Box FF10)
        - Women's Human Rights Education project, correspondence (Box FF10)
      - NED journal, 1996-1997 (Box FF10)
      - Grant, 1997-1998
        - Amendments, program (Box FF10)
        - Drawdown (Box FF10)
        - Periodic financial reports, 3 folders (Box FF10)
        - Project evaluation (Box FF10)
    - NED (Box FF11)
      - Grant, 1997-1998
        - Proposals, 2 folders (Box FF11)
      - Grant 98-302, 1998-1999
        - Agreement, provisions (Box FF11)
        - Drawdown (Box FF11)
        - Financial report (Box FF11)
        - MRE coordinator proposal (Box FF11)
        - Narrative reports (Box FF11)
      - Grant 98-631, 1998-1999
        - Audit (Box FF11)
        - Correspondence (Box FF11)
        - Drawdowns (Box FF11)
        - Financial reports (Box FF11)
        - Periodic reports, 2 folders (Box FF11)
        - Women's Human Right Education proposal, phase II, part II (Box FF11)
      - SIGI/Jordan, 1998 (Box FF11)
      - Building Local Leaders Initiative proposal, 1999-2001, 2 folders (Box FF11)
      - Grant 98-631, notice of closing, 2000 (Box FF11)
    - NED (Box FF12)
      - Grant proposal, 2000-2001 (Box FF12)
    - Netherlands funding, Eldis, Swedish International Development Cooperation Agency (SIDA), info, 2000-2001 (Box FF12)
    - Newman's Own, Inc., inquiry, 2001 (Box FF12)
    - Niwano Peace Foundation, inquiry, 1998 September (Box FF12)
    - Norman Foundation, info, 1998-2001, 2 folders (Box FF12)
    - NOVIB, inquiries, 1997-1998 (Box FF12)
    - Oak Foundation, info, 1998 (Box FF12)
    - Peace Development Fund, info, 1997-1998 (Box FF12)
    - Pennsylvania Coalition Against Violence, annual report, 1998 (Box FF12)
    - The Pew Charitable Trust, info, 1998 (Box FF12)
    - Public Welfare Foundation, info, 1998, 2001, 2 folders (Box FF12)
    - The Rachel and Ben Vaughan Foundation, correspondence, support for lecture series, 1996-1999 (Box FF12)
    - Reebok Human Rights Foundation, 2001 (Box FF12)
    - Resist, Inc., 1998 (Box FF12)
    - Richard and Rhoda Goldman Fund, info, 2000 (Box FF12)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1995-1999 (Box FF12)
    - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1998 (Box FF12)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1998, 2000 (Box FF12)
    - Royal Bank Financial Group, brochure, donations, 2000 (Box FF12)
    - Ruth Turner Fund, 2001 (Box FF12)
    - Samuel Rubin Foundation, proposals, 1998 (Box FF12)
    - San Francisco Foundation, donation, 1998 (Box FF12)
    - Save the Children, inquiry, 1998 (Box FF12)
    - The Sherman Foundation, Inc. 2001 (Box FF12)
    - The Shaler Adams Foundation
      - SIGI annual report, 1994 (Box FF12)
    - The Shaler Adams Foundation (Box FF13)
      - General support, project budget, 1994 (Box FF13)
      - Grants, 1994-1995 (Box FF13)
      - Beijing reception, 1995 (Box FF13)
      - Correspondence, 1995 (Box FF13)
      - CSW meeting, 1995 (Box FF13)
      - Grant for Beijing and Beyond conference, 1995 (Box FF13)
      - Grant request HRE project, 1995 (Box FF13)
      - General support request, 1996 (Box FF13)
      - Correspondence, grants, financial report, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box FF13)
      - Schink, Margaret, correspondence, 1997-1999, 2 folders (Box FF13)
    - The Shefa Fund, 2000 (Box FF13)
    - The Shifting Foundation, 1997 (Box FF13)
    - SIDA, material, 1998 (Box FF13)
    - The Sister Fund
      - Materials, 1997-1998 (Box FF13)
      - Israel proposal, 2000 (Box FF13)
      - Afghan Women Refugees in Pakistan application, 2000-2001 (Box FF13)
    - Soroptimists International, 1998 (Box FF13)
    - Soros Foundation Network, 2000 (Box FF13)
    - The Stanley Foundation, 1995-1998 (Box FF13)
    - Status of Women, Canada, 2000 (Box FF13)
    - The Steven H. and Alida Brill Scheuer Foundation, grant, 1997-1998
      - Israel project, report 2000-2001, 2 folders (Box FF13)
      - Correspondence, 2001 (Box FF13)
    - Stichting Het R.C. Maagdenhuis, 1998 (Box FF13)
    - Tides Foundation
      - Caritas Fund
        - Proposal, 1997 (Box FF13)
    - Tides Foundation (Box FF14)
      - Caritas Fund
        - Grant agreement, narrative report correspondence, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box FF14)
      - Letter of inquiry, 2000 (Box FF14)
    - Turner Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box FF14)
    - UN Office of the Special Adviser on Gender Issues, correspondence with Angela King, 2000 (Box FF14)
    - United Nations Development Programme, GEF Programme, 2000 (Box FF14)
    - United Nations Children's Fund (UNICEF) Gender and Development Section, grant, 1998-1999 (Box FF14)
    - UNIFEM
      - Materials, 1985-1997, 2 folders (Box FF14)
      - Project proposal, 1994 (Box FF14)
      - Jordan conference
        - Proposal, budget, 1998 (Box FF14)
        - Updates for VAW proposals, 1998 (Box FF14)
        - Grant adjustment, 2000 (Box FF14)
      - HRE/KPP project
        - Proposal, 1998 (Box FF14)
        - General, 1999 (Box FF14)
      - Reports to UNIFEM
        - Financial, July 1998-Apr. 2000, 2 folders (Box FF14)
    - UNIFEM (Box FF15)
      - Reports to UNIFEM
        - Midterm, 2000 Feb. (Box FF15)
        - Final, 2000 Jan.-Sept. (Box FF15)
        - Final, 2000 Oct. (Box FF15)
      - VAW project
        - Proposal, budget, approval, manual, 1997-1998 (Box FF15)
        - Final reports, 1998-2000 (Box FF15)
        - Media proposal (Box FF15)
        - A/P section, 2000 (Box FF15)
        - Correspondence with Mika Ichihara, 2000 (Box FF15)
      - Budget revision, 2001 (Box FF15)
      - Correspondence, 2001
        - General (Box FF15)
        - Ishikawa, Shoko, Jan. 5 (Box FF15)
        - UNIFEM Canada, July 5 (Box FF15)
      - Letters to field coordinators (Box FF15)
    - United Methodist Church, correspondence, grant, 1998 (Box FF15)
    - Urgent Action Fund, 1999 (Box FF15)
    - United States Institute of Peace (USIP), application guidelines, 2000 (Box FF15)
    - Vanguard Foundation, correspondence, 1997-1998 proposal, 1998 June 1 (Box FF15)
    - VDay Foundation, proposal, 1998 Mar. 1 (Box FF15)
    - W. Jones Alton Foundation, info, 2000 Jan. 19 (Box FF15)
    - Wallace Global Fund, info, 2000 Jan. 19 (Box FF15)
    - War on Want, info, 1998 (Box FF15)
    - Weltkirche, inquiry, 1998 (Box FF15)
    - Westminster Foundation for Democracy, info, 1997-1998 (Box FF15)
    - W.K. Kellogg Foundation
      - Materials, 1998, Aug. (Box FF15)
      - Information, 2000 (Box FF15)
    - Women, Children, and Family, applications, 2000-2002, 2 folders (Box FF15)
    - Women and Development, inquiry, 2000, Oct. (Box FF15)
    - Women Helping Others, info, 2000 (Box FF15)
    - Women's Asylum, info, 2001 (Box FF15)
    - Women's Health Action Foundation, inquiry, 1998 (Box FF15)
    - Women's Peacepower Foundation, info, correspondence, 1998 (Box FF16)
    - World Bank, info, proposal, 2000 (Box FF16)
    - World Education, inquiry, 1998 (Box FF16)
  - Other Records Subseries, 1985-2003 and undated, bulk 1997-2001, 4 boxes
    Documents related to the maintenance of SIGI’s office and website, mailing lists, records of SIGI’s move to Canada and the closure of the Maryland office, as well as an overview of SIGI’s institutional records, mainly comprised of annual and financial reports. The Publicity section contains interviews and articles about SIGI’s HRE workshops in the Middle East, and a review of SIGI's manual Claiming Our Rights.
    Organized alphabetically. (Six disks originally located with these materials can now be found in the Electronic Formats Series.)
    - Bell Canada (Box OR1)
      - Phone and fax transfer and high-speed subscription, 2001 (Box OR1)
      - Phone lines and internet accounts, 2000 (Box OR1)
      - Reimbursement for original deposit, 2002 (Box OR1)
      - Second domain name transfer, 2000 (Box OR1)
    - Calendar of meetings, 1996-1999 (Box OR1)
    - Computers
      - Purchase and documents, 1997-2000 (Box OR1)
      - Recycling, East-West Foundation, 1994-1997 (Box OR1)
    - Contacts
      - Database info, undated (Box OR1)
      - Database lists, until 2000 Jan. (Box OR1)
      - Gender consultants database, 2001 (Box OR1)
      - Groups, NGOs, and media, 2001 and undated (Box OR1)
      - List of SIGI and SIGN members, 1994-1996 (Box OR1)
      - Media, 2000-2002 and undated (Box OR1)
      - NGOs, Women's Studies, etc., fax and mailing lists, 1995-2003 and undated (Box OR1)
      - Resources, 2001 (Box OR1)
      - SIGA (SIG Alert System) mailing lists (Box OR1)
    - Institutional documents overview, 1985-2000, Folders 1-3 of 8 (Box OR1)
    - Institutional documents overview, 1985-2000, Folders 4-8 of 8 (Box OR2)
    - Library list, undated (Box OR2)
    - Miscellaneous documents, 1998-1991 (Box OR2)
    - Move to Canada
      - Budget, 1999 (Box OR2)
      - Correspondence with Greta Nemiroff regarding move, 1999-2000 (Box OR2)
      - Correspondence with security storage, United Van Lines, 1999 (Box OR2)
      - Customs documents, 1998-1999 (Box OR2)
      - Initial bank account, 1999-2000 (Box OR2)
      - Inventory lists, 1999 (Box OR2)
      - Letters of support for the move, 1999-2000 (Box OR2)
      - Letters to Steering Committee, 2000 (Box OR2)
      - Memos regarding move
        - Final memos from Bethesda, 2000 (Box OR2)
    - Move to Canada (Box OR3)
      - Memos regarding move
        - From Bethesda regarding account, 2000 (Box OR3)
        - Update of tasks from Washington, financial figures, 1999-2000 (Box OR3)
      - Proposal, 1999 (Box OR3)
      - Receipts, 2000
        - General (Box OR3)
        - UPS (Box OR3)
      - Responses to letters about SIGI move, 2000 (Box OR3)
      - Transition
        - Binder, 2000 (Box OR3)
        - Letter for contacts, with lists, 1999 (Box OR3)
        - Letter to funders, 2000 (Box OR3)
        - Letter for SIGI members, 2000 (Box OR3)
      - Transport documents, 1999-2000 (Box OR3)
      - Washington tasks, 1999 Dec. 31 (Box OR3)
    - Office closure
      - Documents shipping, 2001 (Box OR3)
      - Announcements
        - To members and responses, 2001 (Box OR3)
        - To members of Executive Committee, 2001 (Box OR3)
        - To Steering and Advisory committees, and responses, 2001 (Box OR3)
      - Change of address, Canada Post, 2001 Jan. 5 (Box OR3)
      - Change of letterhead, business cards, Denise Cotte, 2001 (Box OR3)
      - Correspondence with Atwater Library and Janet Ilavsky, 2001 (Box OR3)
      - Dismantling of computer network and back-up, 2001 (Box OR3)
      - Estimate of cost, 2001 (Box OR3)
      - Pitney Bowes leasing contract termination, 2001 (Box OR3)
      - Printing new letterhead paper and business cards, post-move, 2001 (Box OR3)
      - Responses from general public, 2001 (Box OR3)
    - Outreach
      - General, 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box OR3)
      - KPP, 1998-1999 (Box OR3)
      - UNESCO, 1997 (Box OR3)
      - UN Refugee Agency, 1997 (Box OR3)
    - Personnel
      - Assistant search, 1999 (Box OR3)
      - French test, 1999 (Box OR4)
      - Greta Hofmann Nemiroff, CV, 1999 (Box OR4)
      - Intern, Ishii Masako, 1999 (Box OR4)
      - Office coordinator position
        - Leila Bedeir materials, 1999 (Box OR4)
        - Pilon, Natalie, 1999 (Box OR4)
      - Office manager job description, 1999 (Box OR4)
      - Policies
        - General, 1996-1999, 3 folders (Box OR4)
        - Conflict of interest, 2001 May (Box OR4)
    - Publicity
      - Beyond Beijing, 1997 (Box OR4)
      - HRE, 1998 (Box OR4)
      - HRE and legal literacy workshop, Lebanon
        - An-Nahar Daily, 1998 Nov. (Box OR4)
        - As-Safir Daily, 1998 Nov. (Box OR4)
        - The Daily Star, 1998 Nov. (Box OR4)
      - HRE Jordan, 1999 (Box OR4)
      - HRE workshop in Azerbaijan, Khazar View, 1998 Sept. (Box OR4)
      - Interview, Building on Indigenous Conception, Al-Raida, 1996 (Box OR4)
      - Islamic Law and Human Rights Today, Interights Bulletin, 1996 (Box OR4)
      - Middle East Newsletter, 1997 Nov. (Box OR4)
      - Marlyn Tadros' journal, interview by Margot Badran, 1997 Mar. (Box OR4)
      - Ms.
        - 1997 Jan.-Feb. (Box OR4)
        - New Iranian Laws Target Women, 1998 Sept.-Oct. (Box OR4)
      - New York Times on Claiming Our Rights, 1996 Dec. 29 (Box OR4)
      - Safe and Secure workshop, Jordan, Adastoor Daily, 1998 Aug. 14 (Box OR4)
      - SIGI's update in the Yearbook of International Organizations, 2001 July (Box OR4)
      - Smithsonian flyer, undated (Box OR4)
      - Washington report on Middle East Affairs, 1997 Aug. 13 (Box OR4)
    - Speaking Engagements
      - Pew Fellowships, 1999 May-Sept. (Box OR4)
      - Potential and upcoming, 1998-1999 (Box OR4)
    - Visitors, 1999 (Box OR4)
    - Web
      - Changes to website, 2001 (Box OR4)
      - Designer contract, IGC support letter, 1998-1999 (Box OR4)
      - Disks, 1999 (Box OR4)
      - Server information, 1997 (Box OR4)
      - Website, 1997, 1998 June, 2 folders (Box OR4)